[DOOR OPENS]
(Leonard (entering):)Hey, I just ran into Penny.
She seemed upset about something.
(Sheldon:)I think it's her time of the month.
(Sheldon:)I marked the calendar
for future reference.
(Leonard:)What's with the fish?
(Sheldon:)It's an experiment.
- What happened to your egg research?
- Oh, that was a dead end.
(Sheldon:)Scrambled eggs are as good
as they're ever going to be.
So fish.
I read an article about scientists
who inserted DNA from luminous jellyfish...
(Sheldon:)...into other animals, and I thought,
"Hey, fish nightlights."
(Sheldon:)Fish nightlights.
It's a billion-dollar idea. Shhh!
(Leonard:)Mum's the word.
Are you sure you don't wanna just apologize
to Gablehauser and get your job back?
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, no, no.
No, I have too much to do.